Woodrow Wilson Collection, 1837-1986 (bulk 1883-1924 ): Preliminary Finding Aid MC168
Public Policy Papers
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1810-1992; 17 Volumes; 34 boxes
  - Family, 1876-1992; 16 boxes
    - General, 1876-1992; 1 box (Box 28)
      - To Wilson, Margaret, 1910-1923; 1 box
        - unidentified, undated; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 34)
        - ALS (Photostat), Woodrow, Marion W, 1915; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 35)
        - Printed card (signed by J.P. Tumulty), Woodrow, Thomas, Mrs., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 36)
        - 8 TLsS, Woodbridge, Samuel I, 1910-1922; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 37)
        - 1 wedding announcement, 1915; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 37)
        - 1 presentation card, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Special Correspondence Collections, 1852 January 10-1932; 17 Volumes; 10 boxes
    - Close, Gilbert F., 1918-1919; 17 Volumes; 1 box
      - 17 shorthand notebooks of letters by Wilson, Woodrow, 1919; 17 Volumes (Box 29, Volume 1-17)
      - TLsS (copies of excerpts), Close, Gilbert F, 1918-1919; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Creigh, Thomas, 1910-1914; 1 box
      - TLsS, Creigh, Thomas, 1910-1914; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Droppers, Garrett, 1907-1924; 1 box
      - Inventory, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - 1907, 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - 1911, 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - 1912, 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - 1913, 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - 1914, 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - 1915, 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - 1916, 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - 1917, 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - 1918, 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - 1920, 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - 1922, 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - 1923, 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - 1924, 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Houston, David F., 1911 December 22-1926 August 2; 1 box
      - 1911 December 22, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - 1913 March 13, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - 1913 April 11, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - 1913 April 17, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - 1913 April 19, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - 1913 May 9, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - 1913 June 24, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - 1913 June 18, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - 1913 June 9, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - 1913 June 14, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - 1913 July 16, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - 1913 June 29, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - 1913 August 4, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - 1913 August 18, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - 1913 October 1, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - 1913 December 22, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - 1914 January 1, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - 1914 March 2, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - 1914 June 29, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - 1914 July 22, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - 1914 August 15, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - 1914 September 21, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 22)
      - 1914 October 10, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 23)
      - 1914 October 16, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - 1914 November 13, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - 1914 December 14, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 26)
      - 1914 December 23, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 27)
      - 1915 January 14, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 28)
      - 1915 February 17, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 29)
      - 1915 March 1, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 30)
      - 1915 March 9, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 31)
      - 1915 May 13, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 32)
      - 1915 June 11, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 33)
      - 1915 September 23, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 34)
      - 1915 October 16, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 35)
      - 1915 December 2, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 36)
      - 1916 February 16, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 37)
      - 1918 March 14, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 38)
      - 1916 March 21, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 39)
      - 1916 March 31, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 40)
      - 1916 April 3, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 41)
      - 1916 May 30, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 42)
      - 1916 June 29, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 43)
      - 1916 July 31, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 44)
      - 1916 August 5, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 45)
      - 1916 August 11, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 46)
      - 1916 September 14, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 47)
      - 1916 October 6, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 48)
      - 1916 November 18, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 49)
      - 1917 January 3, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 50)
      - 1917 January 23, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 51)
      - 1917 January 25, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 52)
      - 1917 February 3, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 53)
      - 1917 March 26, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 54)
      - 1917 April 14, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 55)
      - 1917 April 16, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 56)
      - 1917 April 19, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 57)
      - 2 ANsS, undated; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 58)
      - 1917 May 16, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 59)
      - 1917 June 9, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 60)
      - 1917 June 12, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 61)
      - 1917 June 20, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 62)
      - 1917 July 16, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 63)
      - 1917 July 21, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 64)
      - 1917 July 23, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 65)
      - 1917 July 25, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 66)
      - 1917 July 28, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 67)
      - 1917 August 14, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 68)
      - 1917 August 17, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 69)
      - 1917 August 23, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 70)
      - 1917 November 19, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 71)
      - 1917 November 19, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 72)
      - 1917 November 28, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 73)
      - 1918 January 14, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 74)
      - 1918 January 18, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 75)
      - 1918 January 24, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 76)
      - 1918 February 13, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 77)
      - 1918 February 23, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 78)
      - 1918 March 4, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 79)
      - 1918 March 29, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 80)
      - 1918 April 2, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 81)
      - 1918 April 8, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 82)
      - 1918 April 8, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 83)
      - 1918 April 17, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 84)
      - 1918 May 8, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 85)
      - 1918 May 16, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 86)
      - 1918 June 1, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 87)
      - 1918 June 10, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 88)
      - 1918 July 25, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 89)
      - 1918 July 26, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 90)
      - 1918 July 26, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 91)
      - 1918 July 29, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 92)
      - 1918 August 31, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 93)
      - 1918 September 5, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 94)
      - 1918 September 6, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 95)
      - 1918 September 7, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 96)
      - 1918 September 20, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 97)
      - 1918 September 23, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 98)
      - 1918 November 18, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 99)
      - 1918 November 22, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 100)
      - 1919 March 12, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 101)
      - 1919 August 14, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 102)
      - 1919 August 26, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 103)
      - 1919 September 16, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 104)
      - 1920 February 2, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 105)
      - 1920 May 18, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 106)
      - 1920 July 6, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 107)
      - 1920 July 6, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 108)
      - 1920 August 19, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 109)
      - 1920 September 1, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 110)
      - 1920 December 20, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 111)
      - 1921 February 25, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 112)
      - 1921 March 14, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 113)
      - 1921 December 8, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 114)
      - 1922 January 11, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 115)
      - 1922 April 25, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 116)
      - 1922 May 3, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 117)
      - 1922 May 21, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 118)
      - 1922 May 30, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 119)
      - 1923 March 16, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 120)
      - 1923 December 29, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 121)
      - 1925 April 3, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 122)
      - 1926 August 2, 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 123)
      - 2 ANsS, undated; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 124)
    - Hulbert, Mary A., dates not examined; 1 box
      - "Bermuda", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Table of Contents, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Part I: Letters 4-18, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Part II: Letters 19-42, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Part III: Letters 43-60, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Part IV: Letters 61-100, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Part V: Letters 101-141, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Part VI: Letters 142-165, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Part VII: Letters 166-204, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Table of Contents, Corrections, "Bermuda", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Part I: Letters 1-18, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Part II: Letters 19-42, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Part III: Letters 43-60, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Part IV: Letters 61-100, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Part V: Letters 101-141, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Part VI: Letters 142-165, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Part VII: Letters 166-204, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Thackwell Correspondence and Photographs, 1852 January 10-1924 March 7; 1 box
      - 1 TLS to Woodrow, Hattie; Baldwin, Mary D, 1886 March 20; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - 2 ALsS to Woodrow, Hattie; Wells, Bones, Helen Woodrow, 1913 February 17; 1915 December 26; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - 1 ALS to Woodrow, Herbert; Bones, Helen Woodrow, 1913 December 12; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - 1 ALS to Welles, Hattie Woodrow; Sayre, Jesse Wilson, 1913 November 15; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - 2 ALsS to Welles, Charles B., Welles, Hattie Woodrow, 1913 May 8; 1917 February 5; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - 1 ALS to Woodrow, J. Wilson; Welles, Hattie Woodrow, 1913 May 8; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - 2 ALsS to Wells, Hattie Woodrow; Wilson, Edith Bolling, 1915 December 31; 1924 March 7; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - 1 ALS to Woodrow, Thomas; Wilson, Jeanne Woodrow, 1852 January 10; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - 2 ALsS to Woodrow, Hattie; Wilson, Woodrow, 1880 April; 1880 September 5; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - 2 ALsS to Woodrow, Hattie; Wilson, Woodrow, 1881 January 15; 1881 April 22; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - 2 ALsS to Woodrow, Hattie; Wilson, Woodrow, 1, undated; 1881 May 10; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - 3 ALsS to Woodrow, Hattie; Wilson, Woodrow, 1881 September 26; 1881 October 3; 1881 October 1; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - 1 ALS, 2 TLsS to Wells, Hattie Woodrow; Wilson, Woodrow, 1902 June 27; 1912 September 14; 1913 December 2; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - 3 TLsS to Wells, Hattie Woodrow; Wilson, Woodrow, 1914 August 24; 1915 October 16; 1921 April 11; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - 4 TLsS to Thackwell, Helen Welles, Wilson, Woodrow, 1918 March 29; 1918 July 3; 1920 October 4; 1920 October 25; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Telegram to Thackwell, Helen Welles, Wilson, Woodrow, 1918 July 1; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - 5 TLsS to Woodrow, Helen, (Mrs. Thomas Woodrow, Sr.), 1912 November 9; 1913 March 6; 1914 August 22; 1916 September 30; 1916 December 20; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - AL (copy) with ANS by Woodrow, James Wilson, to Woodrow, Thomas, 1885 June 8; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - 4 TLsS to Woodrow, James Wilson, 1901 July 30; 1902 June 30; 1908 November 21; 1918 June 24; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Program of concert, "In Memoriam", 1924 February 24; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Newspaper clippings, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - 1 ALS to Woodrow, Thomas, n.d., also contains ALS by Woodrow, Helen Still to Woodrow, Thomas, Woodrow, Hattie A., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - Newspaper clipping, Woodrow, James, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - 1 ALS to Woodrow, Hattie A.; Woodrow, James H, 1887 September 29; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 23A)
      - 3 ALsS to Woodrow, Thomas; Woodrow, Robert, 1852 August 5; 1852 November 30; 1853 May 21; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - 10 ALsS to Woodrow, Hattie; Woodrow, Thomas and Woodrow, Helen Jill, 1879-1885; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 25)
      - AD from account book, "Estimate of Value" newspaper clipping, Woodrow, Thomas, 1873 February 1; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 26)
      - TLs (copies), Thackwell collection of photographs, Thackwell Correspondence, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 27)
      - Bones, Jesse Wilson, Bones, Marion Woodrow, Bones, James W., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 28)
      - Bones, Jesse Wilson and Chillicothe, Ohio School House photographs, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 29)
      - Bones, Marion McGraw and Bones, Helen Woodrow, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 30)
      - Welles, Edward Freeman, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 31)
      - Wilson, Joseph Ruggles, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 32)
      - Wilson, Joseph Ruggles, Woodrow, Thomas, Woodrow, James, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 33)
      - Wilson, Joseph Ruggles, Wilson, Joseph Ruggles Jr., Wilson, Annie and Marion, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 34)
      - Wilson, Joseph Ruggles, Wilson, Joseph Ruggles Jr., and Howe, Wilson, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 35)
      - Wilson, Woodrow, dates not examined; 4 folders (Box 34, Folder 36-39)
      - Wilson, Woodrow, Woodrow, Hattie A., and Axson (Wilson), Ellen Louise, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 40)
      - Woodrow, Hattie A., Woodrow, Helen, Woodrow, Thomas R., Woodrow, Herbert H., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 41)
      - Woodrow, Hattie A., Woodrow, James Wilson, and Welles, Edward Freeman, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 42)
      - Woodrow, Hattie A., Donnan, Etta, Bones, Jesse, McGraw Bones, Marion, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 43)
      - Woodrow, Hattie A., Bones, Jesse, Bones, Helen, and McGraw Bones, Marion, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 44)
      - Woodrow, Helen Sill and Woodrow, Thomas, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Wescott, John Wesley, 1910-1932; 1 box
      - Correspondence by Wilson, Woodrow to Wescott, John W., 1910-1919; 1 box
        - 4 TLS (with 1 photostat), 1910; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 1)
        - 7 TLsS, 1911; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 2)
        - 10 TLsS, 1912; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 3)
        - 1 telegram, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 3)
        - 4 TLsS, 1913; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 4)
        - 3 TLsS, 1913; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 5)
        - 5 TLsS, 1914; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 6)
        - 1 TLS, 1914; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 7)
        - 2 TLsS, 1915; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 8)
        - 1 TLS Xerox, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 8)
        - 1 TLS, 1915; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 9)
        - 1 TLS, 1915; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 10)
        - 2 TLsS, 1916; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 11)
        - 4 TLsS, 1916; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 12)
        - 1 TLS, 1917; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 12A)
        - 1 TLS, 1918; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 13)
        - 5 TLsS, 1918; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 14)
        - 1 TLS, 1919; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 15)
        - 1 TLS, 1919; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence by Wescott, John to Wilson, Woodrow, 1918; 1 box
        - TL (carbon) by Wescott, John to Wilson, Woodrow, 1918; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence of others about Wilson, Woodrow, 1911-1919; 1 box
        - 1 TLS, Baker, Newton Diehl, 1916; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 17A)
        - 14 TLsS, McAdoo, William Gibbs, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 18)
        - 11 TLsS, Tumulty, Joseph P, 1911-1917; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 19)
        - 3 ALsS, 1919; undated; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 20)
        - 1 ACS, Wilson, Edith Bolling, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 20)
        - 1 ALS, Wilson, Ellen Louise Axson, 1912; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 21)
        - 1 ALS, Wilson, Jessie, 1912; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence by others about Wilson to Wescott, Ralph W. and Wescott, Harry D., 1917-1932; 1 box
        - 1 TLS (Wescott, Ralph W.) Bolling, John Randolph, 1923; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 23)
        - 1 TLS (with clipping) (Wescott, Ralph W.) Crate, J.G., 1924; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 24)
        - 1 TLS (Wescott, Harry D.), McAdoo, William G, 1917; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 25)
        - 1 TLS (Wescott, Ralph W.), Roosevelt, Franklin D, 1932; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 26)
      - Copies of Wescott Collection, dates not examined; 1 box
        - Xerox, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 27)
        - Carbon copies, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Woods, Lawrence, 1904-1925; 1 box
      - List of abbreviations, List of letters (incomplete), Woods, Lawrence C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - 1 TL (Carbon), Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1904; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - 2 TLs (carbons), Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1906; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - 1 TLS by Hibben, John Grier to Woods, Lawrence C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - 1 printed letter signed by Wilson, Woodrow, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - 2 TLsS Wilson, Woodrow to Woods, Lawrence C, 1907; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - 1 TL (carbon) Woods, Lawrence C, to Wilson, Woodrow, 1907; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - 2 TLs (carbons), Woods, Lawrence C, to Wilson, Woodrow, 1908; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - 7 TLsS, Wilson, Woodrow to Woods, Lawrence C, 1909; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - 10 TLS (Carbons), 1 Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1909; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - 1 TL (carbon), Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1909; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - 2 clippings, 1909; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - 12 TLsS, Wilson, Woodrow to Woods, Lawrence C, 1910; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - 15 TLs (carbons), Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1910; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - 1 ALS, Ellen Axson Wilson to Woods, Lawrence C, 1910; 1 box (Box 36)
      - 5 TLsS, Wilson, Woodrow to Woods, Lawrence C, 1911; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - 5 TLS (carbons), Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1911; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - 3 TLsS, Tumulty, J.P., to Woods, Lawrence C, 1911; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - 1 ASLS, Wilson, Ellen Louise Axson to Woods, Lawrence C, 1911; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - 1 TL (carbon), Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Ellen Louise Axson, 1911; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - 7 TLsS, Wilson, Woodrow to Woods, Lawrence C, 1912; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - 14 TLS (carbons), Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1912; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - 2 telegrams (carbons), Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1912; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - 3 TLsS, Tumulty, J. P. to Woods, Lawrence C., 1 TL (carbon), Woods, Lawrence C. to Tumulty, J. P, 1912; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - 1 TKS, Measday, Walter to Woods, Lawrence C, 1912; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - 2 TLsS, Shea, J.B. to Woods, Lawrence C, 1912; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - 12 TLsS, Wilson, Woodrow to Woods, Lawrence C, 1913; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - 17 TLS (carbons), Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1913; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - 7 TLsS, Tumulty, J. P. to Woods, Lawrence C, 1913; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - 2 TLS (carbons), Woods, Lawrence C. to Tumulty, J. P, 1913; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - 1 TLS, J. W. C. to Woods, Lawrence C, 1913; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - 1 ALS, Bones, Helen Woodrow, to Woods, Lawrence C, 1913; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - 1 TL (carbon), Woods, Lawrence C. to McAdoo William G, 1913; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - 1 TL (memorandum), Woods, Edward A., to Woods, Lawrence C, 1913; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - 15 TLsS, Wilson, Woodrow to Woods, Lawrence C, 1914; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - 1 printed card, Woods, Lawrence C, 1914; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - 6 TLs (carbons), Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1914; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - 1 TLS, Tumulty, J. P., to Woods, Lawrence C, 1914; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - 7 TLsS, Wilson, Woodrow to Woods, Lawrence C, 1915; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - 1 printed letter, 1915; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - 7 TLS (carbons), Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1915; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - 4 TLsS, Tumulty, J. P., to Woods, Lawrence C, 1915; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - 2 TLs (carbons), Woods, Lawrence C. to Tumulty, J. P, 1915; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - 1 TLS, S. S. M. to Woods, Lawrence C, 1915; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - 9 TLsS, Wilson, Woodrow to Woods, Lawrence C, 1916; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - 3 TLs (carbons), Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1916; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - 3 TLsS, Tumulty, J. P., to Woods, Lawrence C, 1916; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - 1 TL (carbon), Woods, Lawrence C. to Tumulty, J. P, 1916; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - 1 TLC, Vc McC to Woods, Lawrence C, 1916; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - 4 TLsS, Wilson, Woodrow to Woods, Lawrence C, 1917; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - 9 TLs (Carbons), Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1917; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - 2 TLsS, Tumulty, J. P., to Woods, Lawrence C, 1917; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - 1 telegram (copy), Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1917; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - 1 printed letter, 1917; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - 4 TLsS, Wilson, Woodrow to Woods, Lawrence C, 1918; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - 6 TLs (carbons), Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1918; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - 4 TLsS, Tumulty, J. P., to Woods, Lawrence C, 1918; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - 1 TL (carbon), Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1919; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - 3 TLsS, Tumulty, J. P., to Woods, Lawrence C, 1919; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - 2 TLS (carbons), Woods, Lawrence C. to Tumulty, J. P, 1919; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - 1 TLS, Palmer, Lew R. to Woods, Lawrence C, 1919; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - 1 TL (carbon), Woods, Lawrence C. to Palmer, Lew R, 1919; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - 1 TLS, R. to Woods, Lawrence C, 1919; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - 2 TLS, Tumulty, J. P., to Woods, Lawrence C, 1920; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - 2 TLsS, Wilson, Woodrow to Woods, Lawrence C, 1920; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 16A)
      - 5 TLsS (carbons), Woods, Lawrence C. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1920; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 16a)
      - 2 ALsS, Wilson, Edith Bolling to Woods, Lawrence C, 1920; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 16a)